

A Marketing Professional with entry-level experience specializing in social media marketing, sales, product marketing, and copywriting. Adept at collaborating with creative teams to drive exposure for new products and brands,

123 Your Street, New York, NY 12345 th e resad I a mond@exa m ple.co m (123) 456-7890

# **Professional Experience**

#### Marketing Intern

Sunlight Watches Inc., New York, NY May 2021 - Present

- Coordinate with marketing specialists, product managers, and social media marketing staff to develop campaigns to support the launch of new smartwatch products
- Analyze competitors and conduct research on target markets to create brand messaging that resonates with the customer base
- Improve followership across Facebook, Twitter, and Instagram by 100%-150% by identifying optimal release times for posts and creating quality marketing copy
- Create presentations for the marketing team featuring marketing indicators and KPIs

#### Education

Bachelor of Science (B.S.)

Marketing

Columbia University, New York, NY

September 2017 - May 2021

### **Key Skills**

- Marketing Strategy
- Social Media Marketing
- Campaign Development
- Copywriting
- ♦ Competitive Analysis

## Academic Experience

## Marketing Projects

Columbia University, New York, NY September 2020- May 2021

 Conducted a project to creates marketing strategy and develop campaigns fora hypothetical startup company in a crowded market by creating marketing materials to educate potential customers on product use cases